Guide to the Marshall Bond Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1888-1926; Series IV; 0.54; (1 box) + 1 volume
  - Commercially produced photographs of the Klondike region and Dawson
    - E. A. Hegg, 32 views of Chilkoot Pass, Klondike River, and Dawson, signed in the negative, 1898-1904 (Box 5, Folder 102-103)
      Many are also stamped in the negative: "By F. H. Nowell"
    - Larss and Duclos, "Midnight Bird's Eye View of Dawson," and two photos of mines and miners, 1899-1901 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Case and Draper, one photo of Miles Canyon on the Klondike River (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - M. Craig, one photo of Dawson by the light of Aurora Borealis [owned by Frank H. Nowell], 1908 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Unidentified photographers, 9 photos of Dawson, Forty Mile, Northwest Mounted Police, boats, and miners (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Studio portrait of MB with E. Reeve Merritt and General Snyman, Mexico, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Goldfield, Nevada snapshots, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Bond family and house and grounds at New Park, Santa Clara, California, ca. 1906 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - New Park, Santa Clara, California, home of Hiram G. and Laura Bond, [ca. 1906] (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Jarbridge, Nevada, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Photograph album of a shooting trip, Stikine River, British Columbia, 1911- (Box 6)
  - Photo album and diary of trip to Lincoln County, New Mexico, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Commercial reproductions of photos of Billy the Kid and associates, the James Gang, and other wild west figures (Box 5, Folder 114)
    Some bear stamps on the verso identifying them as "prints from the Famous Rose Collection of Old Time Photographs. N. H. Rose, Photographer"
  - MB in middle age, studio portrait, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Judge Hiram G. Bond ("Judge Miller" in The Call of the Wild ), undated (Box 8, Folder 146)
- Restricted Fragile, 0.21; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 7 contains fragile originals. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 11 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Box 1, folder 14 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Box 1, folder 25 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Box 1, folder 28 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Box 1, folder 30 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Box 1, folder 32 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Box 1, folder 35 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Box 1, folder 35 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Box, 2, folder 36 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Box 2, folder 37 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Box 2, folder 38 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Box 2, folder 41 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Box 2, folder 42 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Box 2, folder 43 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Box 2, folder 45 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Box 2, folder 48 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Box 2, folder 50 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Box 2, folder 51 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Box 2, folder 53 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Box 2, folder 54 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Box 2, folder 56 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Box 2, folder 57 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Box 2, folder 58 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Box 2, folder 60 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Box 2, folder 63 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Box 2, folder 64 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Box 2, folder 68 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Box 2, folder 71 (Box 7, Folder 144)